<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Платежи Мобикеш</string>

    <string name="faq_question_1_1">How safe is the %1s$ service?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_1_2">I lost my mobile device what should I do?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_1_3">What should I do if I suspect unauthorised activity on my %1s$ account?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_1_4">What do I do if my account has been blocked / suspended?</string>

    <string name="faq_question_2_1">What is the difference between Subscribe, Activate and Guest Mode?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_2_2">Why can\'t I receive my verification code?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_2_3">How will my contact details be used?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_2_4">How long is my payment history kept for?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_2_5">When will my transactions appear on my bank statement?</string>
<!--    <string name="faq_subject_how_works">How %1s$ works</string>-->

    <string name="faq_question_3_1">How old must I be to use %1s$?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_3_2">Where can I pay with %1s$?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_3_3">Will I be charged for using the %1s$ service?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_3_4">How will the retailer / biller / business know I have paid via %1s$?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_3_5">I have entered the wrong bill number and paid the wrong retailer /biller /business. What do I do?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_3_6">What should I do if there is a problem with goods or services, I have paid for using %1s$?</string>

    <string name="faq_question_4_1">Where are my card details stored?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_4_2">What cards can I link to my %1s$ account?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_4_5">My card has expired, what do I do?</string>
    <string name="faq_question_4_6">My card was lost or stolen, what do I do?</string>
    <!--    <string name="faq_question_4_1">How safe is the %1s$ service?</string>-->

    <string name="faq_answer_1_1">%1s$ is extremely secure and has been designed with your security in mind. We have a number of security measures in place. These include:\n\nPIN protection. Just like your card and your mobile phone, the app is protected with a four-digit PIN.\n\nPIN block. If you have forgotten your PIN you are given three attempts to remember it. If you are still unsuccessful after a 30-minute delay you will be given another three attempts to enter the correct PIN. After this you will be referred to the customer services team so that we can verify that you are you.\n\nSecurity questions. If you have set up the security questions and answers (tap on the icon on the righthand corner of the screen and choose the Security questions option), this feature will be offered to you after the first unsuccessful PIN attempt or will automatically kick in after three unsuccessful PIN attempts. If the first security question is answered incorrectly, you will be asked two more questions. If either of these is answered incorrectly, your account will be temporarily blocked until we can verify that you are you.\n\nBiometrics. You can use biometric authentication instead of your PIN. Biometric authentication is available for devices that are equipped with the appropriate scanner.\n\nAutomatic logout. This app is designed to automatically log you out after a few minutes of inactivity. For your own peace of mind, you can adjust this timeframe as you see fit.\n\nUnique identifiers. Both your mobile device and mobile number are linked to your %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% account and act as unique identifiers. This is to ensure that a fraudster cannot access your account from any other device or using a different mobile number (SIM card).\n\nMemPad. MemPad is an easy way to enter your PIN and boasts a non-standard keyboard, making it hard for fraudsters to gain access to your PIN using hacking software to capture keyboard entries.\n\nCard details secure storage. For security reasons your card numbers are not stored on your mobile device. Your details will be stored on a secure server in our certified (worldwide Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard compliant) data centre.\n\nRetailers / billers / businesses do not see your financial details. No financial information is passed on to retailers / billers / businesses when you make payments with this app.\n\n3D Secure. This service uses 3D Secure. 3D Secure (Verified by VISA, MasterCard SecureCode) is an extra layer of security offered to you by your bank when shopping. Each bank has its own 3D Secure verification procedure. When making a payment you will need to follow your bank procedure.?</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_1_2">For security reasons your payment method details are not stored on your mobile device and the app is password protected should it fall into the wrong hands. Once you have recovered or replaced your mobile phone, download the app and activate your account.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_1_3">This situation is highly unlikely as your %1s$ account is linked to your device and phone number (SIM card). Unlike cards or online shopping accounts, your %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% account cannot be used without your knowledge on another device.\n\nIf you still think someone has accessed your account by using your phone without your permission you need to report this activity immediately. There are several options available to you. If you can, sign in to your %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% account and change your PIN. Alternatively, you can request a callback or remove your payment methods at any time by either tapping on the Wallet icon on the Dashboard screen and choosing the delete option or tapping on the icon on the righthand corner of the screen and choosing the Remove all payment methods option.\nOnce the situation has been resolved, you can add a payment method to your account and begin using the service again.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_1_4">Your security is our top priority. If we believe that your account might be at risk, we may block it for security reasons. Your account will only be blocked if certain suspicious actions are performed in your app (for example, there were three incorrect attempts to enter your PIN).\n\nYou will be notified that your account is blocked / suspended via the app and you will be offered an option to request a callback from a customer service representative. You will also have an option to cancel the process and address the situation at your convenience. In this case, the app will redirect you to the Welcome screen. You will need to press Subscribe / Sign in, enter your phone number and request a callback. When your account is blocked, we will have to speak to you in person so that we will be able to establish that you are you and it is safe to reactivate your account.\n\nWe cannot send you an automated reactivation link via email, as some other services choose to do. This is due to the fact that should a fraudster get hold of your phone, they might be able to get access your email and use the link to gain access to your %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% account. If we speak to you in person, we can ensure your account will always be safe and secure.</string>

    <string name="faq_answer_2_1">To get the most benefit from this service and all of the associated advantages, we recommend that you subscribe. Subscribing means that you will have a full %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% account. Should you choose not to subscribe, there is also a guest checkout option, which lets you pay but only offers the basic features of the %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% service.\n\nThe activate option is available to customers that already have a %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% account. This is for when, for example, you are reinstalling the app on a new handset or your account has been deactivated / suspended for security reasons.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_2_2">The most common reason for not receiving an SMS is due to the fact that an incorrect phone number was entered. Please check you have entered the correct number before trying again.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_2_3">We ask for these details so that we can easily contact you and to quickly identify you when we are resolving any problems you may have. Your mobile phone number is a unique identifier and essential should you request a callback. Your email address will be used to send you important updates about your account and our service. You can also request any reports and copies of paid bills to be sent to your email address.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_2_4">Your payment history is available on the app for three calendar years. If you have any queries or wish to see transactions prior to this timeframe, you will need to check your bank / card statement for the card(s) in question. All %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% transactions will appear on your card statement as per normal card transactions.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_2_5">Transactions via %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% are card-based and will appear on your bank statement in the same timeframe that you could expect normal card transactions from your bank to clear. This can be anything from immediately to a couple of days depending on your card issuer.</string>

    <string name="faq_answer_3_1">You need to be 16 years of age or older to use %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME%. By agreeing to our Terms of Service, you are also confirming that you are over 16. Please read these terms carefully to make sure that you abide by the legal requirements of using this service.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_3_2">You can pay using %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% wherever you see the %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% acceptance logo. Should you be in any doubt, you can ask the retailer / biller / business directly. %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% is a new and exciting service that is being rolled out across the UK, Jordan and a few other countries. The list of retailer / biller / business where %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% payments are accepted can be found by tapping the Businesses button on the Service Dashboard screen. %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% designed to pay for goods and services of retailers and businesses, from high street shops, restaurants, market stalls and online retailers, to bill providers (utilities, councils), schools and nurseries, local tradesmen, taxis, charities, clubs and societies, events and many other registered companies that accept payments.\n\nPlease note: to use this service you will need access to the Internet (Wi-Fi or mobile data).</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_3_3">This app is free to download and we do not charge you for using the %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% service. Some retailers / billers / businesses may choose to charge you a small surcharge or comfort fee for using %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% to pay for their goods or services. In this instance, you should be notified before you make a payment. The majority of retailers / billers / businesses will not charge you for using this service. Standard charges set up between you and your bank/card issuer will still apply. Network charges as agreed with your mobile network provider to include data usage may also apply. All text messages that you receive from %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% are free unless abroad or roaming.\n\nTo ensure your transactions are secure when using %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME%, you will need to go through the 3D Secure process as set up by your card issuer. As part of the registration process your card issuer may inform you that your account will be debited one unit of the currency in the account. This is a technical security check only and the transaction will not appear on your account statement. This allows us to verify that your card is not being used fraudulently. Your security is our top priority and as such this is only a test and the money will NOT be taken from you.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_3_4">When you make a payment using %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME%, the bill is marked with a green Paid symbol beneath it.\n\nThe retailer / biller / business will immediately receive notification of your payment either in their own app or cash register, or will see your payment on the list of paid bills at the end of a billing period or upon receiving a copy of your payment order depending on the type of company they are and their chosen integration method.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_3_5">We have a number of safe guards in place to make sure you do not pay the wrong retailer / biller / business when entering the bill by keyboard. However, should this occur we are unable to recall the payment as we are not your bank or the retailer / biller / business; we are facilitating the payment. You may wish to contact your bank to see what options are available to you. Be very careful when entering the bill number. We are not responsible if you make a payment to the wrong retailer / biller / business. Each time you make a payment with the %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% service you are given the opportunity to review the bill details before you pay. To avoid manual bill entry mistakes, we suggest you use the QR Code or NFC payment options.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_3_6">The %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% service is a payment service. Should you have any issues with the goods or services you have purchased, including delivery, you will need to contact the retailer / biller / business directly.</string>

    <string name="faq_answer_4_1">For security reasons your card details are not stored on your mobile device. Your details will be stored on a secure server in our fully certified (PCI DSS compliant) data centre.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_4_2">The %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% service is developed with ease of use in mind. As such, you can link multiple cards to this service. Card types include, debit cards, credit cards, corporate cards and prepaid cards so long as these cards carry the appropriate logo. We are working hard to accept other regional and international card brands and we will keep you updated accordingly.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_4_5">Tap on the Wallet icon on the Service Dashboard screen.\n\nIn this screen you can view all of the payment methods you have set up to use on %SUBST_APPLICATION_NAME% and edit, add or delete cards as you see fit.</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_4_6">If your card is lost or stolen, we strongly advise that you contact your bank / card issuer immediately. Once you have a new card, you can update your card details, by tapping on the Wallet icon on the Dashboard screen.</string>
<!--    <string name="faq_answer_4_1">text</string>-->

</resources>